总算到了
There she is.
老图书馆 曾在里面度过漫漫长夜啊
The old library. That's some late nights in there.
的确有些夜晚是在学习呢 别告诉老妈
Some of them I even spent studying. Don't tell your mom.
那就不该告诉我
And maybe don't tell me.
大学生
College!
他举起手是为了挡阳光 免得晃眼
He was shielding his eyes from the sun.
击掌时才反应过来
Knew it when I hit it.
菲尔要带海莉拜访他的母校
Phil is taking Haley to visit his alma mater.
深爱的大学
Loved college.
我们希望父亲的激情也激起女儿对大学的向往
Mm, we were hoping some of that enthusiasm rubs off on her.
加油 "斗牛蛙"队
Go Bullfrogs!
是斗牛犬队
Dogs!
斗牛犬队
Bulldogs!
我觉得你是故意的
I feel like you do that on purpose.
不 只是
No, it's just...
我知道是"斗牛" 就是忘记是"蛙"还是"犬"了
I say "bull", and I can't remember it's frogs or dogs.
我跟大学哥们打电话时
When I talk to my old branch from college.
我们是"呱呱"叫 还是"汪汪"叫
do we croak or do we bark?
我来接
I got it.
喂
Hello?
不是吧
No way!
不是吧 海莉 快来看
Haley, no way! Check it out!
我和哥们喝完啤酒后 会跳到这些午餐盘上
After a few beers, my buds and I would jump on these lunch trays
就从这坡上比赛滑下去 上来试试
and race down this same hill. Hop on.
-我不想试 -不骗你 你马上就会傻乐
- I don't want to to hop on. - Seriously, you'll get the giggles.
我不想傻乐
I don't want the giggles.
喂 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
-游览进行得怎样 -非常好
- How's the trip going? - So good.
加油 斗牛蛙队
Go, Bullfrogs.
是"犬"
It's dogs.
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
海莉表现怎样
How's Haley doing?
她啊
She's...
她喜欢 她喜欢这里
She's loving it. She's loving it.
我带她去看了学生会 参观了宿舍
I showed her the student union. We visited the dorms.
我们去教室听了节课
We sat in on a class.
我觉得她开始发现大学的美好了
I really think she's starting to see what college has to offer.
克莱尔 稍等
Oh, hang on, Claire.
加油 斗牛犬
Go, Bulldogs!
曼尼 这个叫贝拉的女孩是谁
Manny, who is this Bella girl?
你的笔记本上怎么满是她的名字
And why is her name all over your notebook?
妈 贝拉已经不是小女孩了
Bella's no girl, mom.
她最近开苞了 就像四月的丁香花
She has recently blossomed, like a purple lilac in April.
你说的"开苞"是什么意思
What do you mean, she blossom?
春情躁动期吗
Like, the poo-berty?
没错
Yeah.
我去开门
I'll get it.
歌洛莉亚 你爱看的节目要开始了
Hey, Gloria, your show's about to start.
录下来吧
Record it.
不行 录像机都满了
No, the DVR's filling up.
咱就把它看完算了
Let's just watch and get it over with.
歌洛莉亚总是说
Gloria's always saying
我们应该多些夫妻共享时光
we should do more stuff together.
所以我答应看她喜欢的这部
So I agreed to watch this
疯狂的哥伦比亚肥皂剧
crazy Colombian soap opera she loves.
《肥龟爷髅》
"Fuego y hielo."
显然 就是"长发鬼之乱吼"的西班牙语叫法
Which apparently, is Spanish for "Big hair and yelling."
"水深火热"
"Fire and ice."
讲的是人间疾苦
It's about human suffering.
人家可喜欢了
I relate to it.
我是说 那家伙是个法官 总该穿件衣裳
I'm just saying, the guy's a judge. He can put a shirt on.
哎呀 那是什么
Ay, what is that?
没什么
Oh, nothing.
那可不像"没什么"哦 里面是什么
That doesn't look like a nothing. What is inside?
只是我买的点东西
Oh, it's just something I bought.
我回房间再拆开
I'm gonna go open it in my room.
可不是什么好现象啊
I don't like this.
曼尼从来不背着我有小秘密
Manny has never kept a secret from me.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
你觉得那是什么东西
What do you think it could be?
我现在担心那东西
Well, right now I'm a little worried
能让你一整晚烦着我
it could be the rest of my evening.
再见 我爱你
Mwah! Bye-bye. Love you.
克莱尔 等等 你有兴趣
Hey, Claire, listen. Uh, if you want,
和其他几位妈妈一起 共赏《乱世佳人》吗
some of the moms are gonna stay and watch "Gone with the wind"
在我家的新放映室哦
in my new screening room.
有葡萄酒喝哦
I got pinot!
我很乐意 可我身体不太舒服
I would love to, but I'm not feeling that great,
所以我还是回家歇着吧
so I'm probably just gonna go home and rest.
况且我看过这电影了
Plus I've seen that movie.
没 我从来没看过《乱世佳人》
No, I never saw "Gone with the Wind,"
但我的俩孩子今晚不回家睡
But I have two kids at sleepovers,
而且菲尔带海莉去外地了
And Haley's out of town with Phil.
所以今晚就我一个人在家
That means I have one night to myself,
这是千载难逢的好机会啊
which happens once every never.
我可不会去和那帮
I am not spending it
高中时就跟我有仇的八卦妈妈们混一晚上
with some gossipy mom who was mean to me in high school.
今晚我要出去找点乐子
I need a fun night out.
真棒
Yes.
这是什么鬼地方 不对
What the hell is this? No.
我是叫你们带我体验狂欢之夜 不是来这儿
I asked you guys for a fun night out, not this.
我要的是纵情歌舞 乌烟瘴气
I-I-I need music and dancing and secondhand smoke.
求你试试这儿吧 绝对超值
Oh, please give this place a chance. It's a great value.
这儿环境舒适
The room is so cozy.
肉馅饼好吃得要命
And the potpies are to die for.
你不觉得你刚说的那些无聊到死吗
Are you really comfortable with what you just said?
拜托 我的派对达人是怎么了
Come on. What happened to the party people
你们以前还带我去锐舞派对 让我穿"魔力挺"
who took me to a rave, and I got to wear a tube top,
我还往艳舞男孩的小内裤里塞钱呢
and I stuffed cash in a caged go-go boy's speedo?
我们依旧是派对达人
We're still party people.
乔安 能给我来杯潘趣酒吗[无酒精]
Oh, Joanne, before I forget, can I get a punch?
差一杯就能有一份免费馅饼了
One away from a free potpie.
如果那是你们的基佬卡 就该吊销了
If that was your gay card, it would be revoked.
克莱尔 你知道吗
Okay, you know what, Claire?
你有点儿像回到高中时代了
You're being a little high school you.
米奇尔 对不起 但我难得一夜自由
I am sorry, Mitchell, but I get one free night,
我不能把一晚上浪费在这
And I can't spend it at a place
威尔森小学的荣誉赞助餐馆
that is a proud supporter of Wilson Elementary.
我们都该回馈社会才对 克莱尔
We all need to give back, Claire.
把大好夜晚"回馈"给我吧
Give me back my night.
好吧 朗吉纳斯邀请我们去个精品店的开业晚宴
Okay, well, Longinus did invite us to a boutique opening,
你懂的 有鸡尾酒和音乐
You know, cocktails, DJ.
但是会很疯很闹的
But it'll--it'll be a whole scene, though.
闹啊 闹好啊 棒极了
A scene? A scene is perfect. That's great.
趁你们还没改变主意 咱们赶紧上车
I will get in the car before you guys change your mind.
快 走吧 出发
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
这么说没馅饼吃咯
So does that mean no potpies?
乔安 两个九号的打包
Uh, hey, Joanne? Two number nines to go.
没说错吧
Was I wrong?
敢说这鸡翅不是你平生未尝的美味吗
Are these not the best wings you've ever had in your life?
-赞不绝口啊 -你还说吃不了40个
- Oh, my god. - And you didn't wanna get 40.
顺便说 这只是美好夜晚的开始喔
Oh, and by the way, this is just the start of your evening.
下一个节目 去方庭
Next up, it's over to the quad
欣赏一组男高音表演 要跟我去吗
for a musical interlude from tenors, anyone?
-是一个全男性声乐团... -我懂的
- It's an all-male singing group... - Got it.
喂 你好
Oh, hey!
你不是今早在我游览队伍里那个吗
Oh, hey. Weren't you on my tour this morning?
对 我叫海莉 这是我老...
Yeah, I'm Haley, and this is my d--
老哥 你信了你信了
Big brother. You bought it for a second.
你好吗 噢糟糕
How are you? Oh, oops.
好吧 不管怎样 你知道吗
Okay. Anyway, you know what?
今晚有个学生联谊会
There is a student mixer going on tonight.
你想去的话 我和其他一些女孩
If you wanna go, me and a bunch of other girls
打算一起过去
are gonna head over there.
噢 那个 我想说 还是算了
Oh! Uh, you know what? That's okay.
我老爸都计划好了
My dad's got this whole thing planned...
不管怎样多谢了
but thank you anyway.
客气 很高兴见到你
No problem. Well, it was nice meeting you.
我也是
Nice meeting you.
多欢乐啊 就我们两个
How fun is this? Just me and you.
我有点紧张
I was a little nervous
怕你没看出这里的独特之处
you wouldn't see what's so special about this place.
我不是逼你一定要考这里 你知道 你
Not that I'm pushing you to come here. You know, you're--
你得自己做决定
You're gonna make your own decisions.
你想跟她们一起去 是不是
You wanna go with them, don't you?
不 按我们的计划来
No, we're doing our thing.
去吧 晚了她们就走了
Yeah, quick. Before they leave.
-真的吗 -去吧 我搞得定
- Are you sure? - Go. I can handle it.
你又不是第一个在满是鸡腿的餐桌前
You're not the first girl to leave me at this table
离我而去的女孩子
with a plateful of chicken wings.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding!
真希望我是开玩笑
I wish I was kidding.
-我... -本不想让你听到的 好好玩
- I... - You weren't supposed to hear that. Have fun.
好的
Okay.
爱你喔
Love you.
鼻子整形了
Nose job.
提臀了
Butt lift.
去年夏天 那玩意儿都快垂到地面了
Last summer, that thing was 4 inches off the ground.
她们屁股上的赘肉都跑哪儿去了
What do they do with all the butt they take out?
我想我知道答案了
I have a theory.
该死 我前男友来了
Oh, damn! Here comes my ex.
-谁啊 兰多夫吗 -还是马可斯
- Who? Randolph? - Marcus?
勒迈克尔吗
LaMichael?
不 是马特 我得走了
No. Matt. I gotta go.
狗血N角恋 好喜欢
Drama. Love it!
姐要的就是这个
This is what I wanted.
谁要再来一杯吗
Who needs a drink?
我还是要点矿泉水吧
I could use a little seltzer water.
再来点香槟吗 克莱尔
More bubbly, Claire?
再来我就"槟至如归"了
Mm, I will be after I get a drink.
看 他那才叫好基友的风范嘛
See, that's what gay is supposed to be like.
你怎么样我不清楚
Okay, I don't know about you,
我内心的激情欢乐只剩5分钟了
but I got about five minutes of fabulous left in me.
我早就幻想自己在咱家厨房里了
Yeah, in my mind, I'm already in our kitchen.
我在看诱人的肉饼在微波炉里旋转
I'm watching my potpie rotate in the microwave.
好吧 好吧 帽子什么时候又流行回来了
Okay. Okay. When did hats come back?
那女人已经来回折腾八趟了
That one's come back about eight times.
老实待一边去吧 老女人
Pick a side of the room, lady.
那啥 那边貌似
All right, there's, like,
有上千人在排队拿酒
a thousand people waiting for wine.
我要试几套衣服
I wanna try on a couple of dresses,
然后朱利安哥带我们去城郊的酒吧玩
And then Julian here's gonna take us to a club across town.
我想我们要回家了
I think we're gonna go home.
啥 为啥 才九点半
What? Why? It's 9:30.
都九点半了
It's 9:30?
什么时候起你们变成居家老妇了
When did you two become such old women?
起初 你们带我去老人院喝麦片粥
First, you take me to that senior center for porridge,
现在连卢克都比你们能熬夜
and now you can't even stay up past Luke's bedtime?
-今天周五 我们都很累 -很疲劳的说
- It's Friday. We get tired on fridays. - We get very tired.
我同时照顾3孩子 累了好多年了
I have 3 children. I've been tired since 2005.
跟姐疯狂去吧 你们开车送我
Let's rally. You're my ride.
如果你想去玩 我可以送你回家
If you want to stay out, I can take you home.
真的吗
Really?
当然
Of course.
那好吧 姐妹们 回家吧
Okay. All right, girls, go home,
长发盘好 关关灯
roll up your hair, clap out the lights,
而这个人 素昧平生
'cause this guy, who I just met,
就能带我出去好好乐一番
is gonna show me a good time.
好吧 如果他是直男
Okay, well, if he was straight,
这会就是高中重现了
this would be just like high school.
剧情太脑残了
This is ridiculous.
明显她在斗篷里藏了把手枪
She's obviously got a pistol under that poncho.
你怎么能看下去啊
How do you watch this stuff?
他都在楼上折腾一个多小时了
He's been up there for more than one hour.
-我受不鸟了 -谁在楼上啊
- I can't stand this. - Who's been up there?
罗纳尔多就在她面前洗碗啊
Ronaldo's doing the dishes right in front of her.
我是说曼尼 在他房间里
Manny, in his bedroom.
歌洛莉亚 你看进去了吗
Gloria, are you even watching this?
我为你才看的
I'm doing this for you.
他到底盒子里藏了什么 不想给我看呢
What does he has in that box that he cannot show to me?
小男孩都会背着妈妈藏秘密
Little boys are supposed to keep secrets from their mothers.
等等 法官从窗缝里偷窥
Wait. The judge just peeked through the window.
他现在看上了西莉亚了吗
Is he interested in Celia now?
她都能当他女儿了
She could be his daughter.
我猜是给我的生日礼物
I bet it's a birthday gift for me.
有道理 他说什么呢
Yeah, that sounds right. What's he saying?
从没见过他这么恼火
I've never seen him this mad.
等一等
Wait a minute.
我已经在他床底下发现给我的生日礼物了
I already found my birthday gift underneath his bed.
是个大帽子
It's a giant hat.
什么时候起 帽子又流行回来了
When did hats came back anyway?
她伸手到斗篷下面了
Now she's reaching under the poncho.
貌似她要朝罗纳尔多开枪
Like she's gonna shoot Ronaldo.
主角怎么会死呢 当观众白痴啊
He's the main character, right?
不管了 我要上去看看
That's it. I'm going up there.
等下 歌洛莉亚 别去
Wait, Gloria. No. Don't go.
-为什么 -你想啊
- Why not? - Think about it.
一个13岁的小男孩 整天思春
13-year-old boy, talks about girls all day long.
我们电脑的绿坝比五角大楼都严密
We have more security on these computers than the Pentagon.
你觉得他在上面会做什么 独自一人
What do you think he's doing up there... Alone?
你觉得他是租了"爱情动作片"吗
Do you think he ordered some movies?
电影 杂志 一切皆有可能
Movies, magazines, whatever the hell.
你怎么可以这么说呢 杰
How dare do you say that, Jay?!
他只是个小男孩 只是个小孩
He's a little boy! He's just a boy.
我不想跟你说话 我要出去走一走
I don't want to talk to you. I'm gonna take a walk.
歌洛莉亚 别这样
Gloria, come on.
回来吧 我知道你不是冲我发火
Come back. I know you're not mad at me.
你只是
You just...
她干了什么
Oh! What'd she do?
罗纳尔多
Ronaldo!
"红中"
Wang chung!
付钱吧 先生们
Pay up, gentlemen!
爽啊
Yes!
多谢了
Thank you!
这么多 真给力
Really? That's so nice.
再来一大罐酒 我的好姑娘
Another pitcher, my good woman.
要是克莱尔知道 肯定会杀了我的
Claire would have killed me if she'd known
我让海莉单独参加派对
that I let Haley go off alone
自己却和一群学生在酒吧玩乐
while I chilled in a bar with some undergrads,
不过我信任我的女儿
But I happen to trust my daughter.
但我还是利用她手机上的GPS来追踪她的位置
Also, I was tracking her location with the GPS on her phone.
各位 洛斯阿拉莫斯是哪儿啊
Fellas, Cedar and Los alamos. That's, uh...
是在派凯屋吗
Pi chi house?
派凯屋
Pi chi?
真是的 我的蓝牙怎么用不了
Oh, come on. Why is my bluetooth not working?
天啊 是朗吉纳斯 他一定很生我们的气
Oh, god. It's Longinus. He's gonna be so mad at us.
朗吉 不要怪我们先走了
Hey, Longe. Don't be mad at us for leaving.
我回到我们那桌 所有人都走了
I went back to our spot, and everybody was gone.
谁会对好姐妹做这种事啊
Who does that to a sister?!
抱歉 可小保姆打电话来
We're sorry, but the sitter called,
说莉莉发烧了
and, uh, lily was running a fever.
所以 我们也很抱歉
So... We feel even worse
把克莱尔丢给你和你的火辣男友
about dumping Claire on you and your hot date.
随便一提 他真是又帅又风趣啊
Who is gorgeous, by the way. Seems super funny, too.
天生一对
Perfect for you.
拜托 我也希望他是我对象
Please, I wish that was a date.
他是我的教练 是个直男
He's my trainer, and he's straight.
什么 朱利安是直男吗 这样才赞呢
What? Julian's straight. Oh, I love it
直男和同志一起出去玩
when a straight person and a gay person go out together.
如果他是同志我会更开心的
I'd love it a lot more if he was gay.
我的天啊 这不是我们的车
Oh, my god. This isn't our car.
-什么 -这不是我们的普锐斯
- What? - This isn't our Prius!
泊车小弟肯定给错车了
They--they must've given us the wrong one at the valet.
所以这蓝牙才用不了
That's why the bluetooth isn't working.
我们偷了一辆车 你说真的吗
We stole a car? Are you serious?
出什么事了
What's happening?
我们偷了别人的车 我们得挂了
Oh, we stole a car. Uh, we gotta go.
我们没偷车 小卡 是别人给错了车
Okay, we did not steal a car, Cam. It was given to us.
你对我大呼小叫干什么 你才是偷车的人
Why are you giving me attitude? You're the one that stole a car.
这怎么能算偷车呢 从何说起
How is this a stolen car?! How?!
我不知道 我都糊涂了
I don't know! I'm confused!
你车上有阿司匹林吗
Do you have an aspirin?
这不是我的车
This isn't my car!
小克 你好啊 出什么事了
Hey, Lukie. Hi. What's going on?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
我找找
I'll check.
在我这儿
I have it.
我可以送过来
Well, I could bring it by
20分钟后在外面见 好吗
and meet you outside in 20 minutes?
不 外面 在外面 亲爱的
No, sw--out--out-- outside, sweetie.
好 一会儿见
Okay. Bye-bye.
你介意顺道去一下我儿子过夜的地方吗
Do you mind swinging by my kid's sleepover?
我得把这个矫牙器给他
I gotta give him this retainer.
就在去酒吧的路上
It's on the way to the club.
当然 没问题
Sure, no problem.
你人太好了
Oh! You are so sweet.
坚实美臂啊 蝙蝠侠 你都泡在健身房吗
Holy pythons, batman. Do you ever leave the gym?
其实我是健身教练兼按摩师
Uh, no. Actually, I'm a trainer and a masseur.
天啊
Oh, my god.
我可得让你按摩一下
I'm gonna have to try out that second one.
帮我拉开拉链
Zip, please.
不得不说
I gotta say,
今晚比我期待得要好玩多了
this night is turning out to be a lot more fun than I expected.
我有两个孩子在别人家过夜
I've got two kids at sleepovers
另一个和她爸出城了
and one upstate with daddy.
好戏才刚刚开始呢
The fun is just beginning.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
泊车小弟把我们的车给了其他人
The valet gave our car away to someone, like,
一个半小时前就给错了
an hour and a half ago.
你知道这意味着什么
You know what that means.
我们的肉馅饼现在有可能在任何地方
Our potpies could be anywhere by now.
他们可能回家了 如果能找到他们的地址
They probably went home. If--if we knew their address,
也许能看看车在不在那儿
maybe we could see if our car was there.
好啊 那你准备怎么找呢
Oh, yeah. And how do you propose we do that?
正在计算回家路线
Calculating route home.
就是这样
Yeah.
你挺能干的嘛
Oh, you're good. Mm.
看 只有半英里多而已
Oh, and look. Only .6 miles away.
在前方500英尺处右转
Prepare to turn right in 500 feet.
听听 她在过路口前
Notice how she didn't wait
竟然知道提醒我 小卡
until after the turn to tell me, Cam?
不是吧 现在要开吵吗
Really? This? Now?
我只是
I'm just...
看 他们去听Jay-Z演唱会了
Oh, look. They went to see Jay-Z.
我们差点就去看Jay-Z了 不是吗
We almost went to see Jay-Z, didn't we?
-没有 谁让它8点半才开始呢 -对
- No, no, no, 'cause remember it started at 8:30. - Oh, yeah,
也就是说到十点才能结束
which meant he wouldn't have gone on until 10:00.
还有那没地停车的噩梦
And then that parking nightmare.
观众席要命的阶梯
Oh, and those stairs.
好 我现在发现问题了
Okay, I'm hearing it now.
克莱尔说的对吗 我们现在很墨守成规
Is Claire right? Are we in a rut?
也许吧 特别是和这些人比
Well, we might be, especially compared to these people.
看这个 去坎昆的行李票
Look at this. Cancun luggage tickets.
优胜美地国家公园的停车票
A parking pass to Yosemite.
铁人三项的号码牌 这才是生活啊
A triathlon bib. This is living.
可是回过头想 我们有莉莉 对吗
No, but you know what? We have Lily, okay?
-我知道 -你带着小孩干不了那些事的
- I know. - You can't do that with a child.
他们也有儿童专用座椅
They have a car seat.
好吧 我们是保守又无聊
Okay, fine, we're in a rut.
目标在前方900英尺
Destination ahead in 900 feet.
也许我们只需要多和
You know, maybe we just need to be around
有带动作用的人在一起
more stimulating people.
前方900英尺内就有这样的人
Well, we're gonna be in about 900 feet.
这主意或许可行 他们看起来是有趣的人
It's not the craziest idea. They seem like fun people.
-没错 也许我们能做伴侣好友 -对
- Yeah, and maybe we can be new couples friends with them. -Yeah.
我们可以一起去听演唱会
You know, we can go out to concerts,
试吃新品 结伴豪华野营
try exciting new food, maybe do some luxury camping.
没错 让我们胸怀他们的大志
Yeah, hitch our wagon to their star
看他们激扬我们的人生
and see how fast they spice up our life.
你已经到了
You have arrived.
我想也到了
I believe we have.
你个傻逼狗娘养的
You dumb son of a bitch!
-我的天啊 -我的天啊
- Oh, my god. - Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
-我的天啊 -什么情况啊
Oh, my god! Oh, my god. What's happening?!
你居然还敢回来 你个劈腿的王八蛋
I can't believe you came back here, you filthy, cheating pig!
她在哪 她在哪
Where is she? Where is she?!
倒车 快点
Back up, I said!
我正倒着呢 但我们"沉轨"了
I'm trying! We are in a rut!
都这会了 你还想谈"成规"的事
Really? You wanna talk about that right now?
不是 我们卡住了 车轮沉在轨里了
No, we are stuck! We're in an actual rut. We're stuck.
我的天啊 我的天啊
Ohh! Oh, my god. Oh, my god!
由爱生恨大发泄 我们惨成受害者
We are victims of a hate crime right now!
-走开 走开 -我的天啊
- Go! Go! -Oh, my god!
不行 想都别想
Oh, no, you don't.
爸 你在这干嘛啊
Dad, what are you doing here?
-这是什么 伙计 -姜汁汽水
- What's this, buddy. - Ginger ale.
是吗 可这闻着像 还真像姜汁汽水
Oh, really? 'cause is smells-- okay, it smells like ginger ale.
但这说明不了什么
But that doesn't prove anything.
-你搞什么啊 -我们该走了
- What the hell? - We are leaving.
我正玩的尽兴呢
I'm having a nice time with--
和这个蠢蛋玩 顺便说一下 你也太老套了
With this clown? And by the way, it's a little cliche
找个和你老爸一个款型的男人
to pick someone who looks exactly like your dad.
我知道你电话 小凯子
I got your number, pi chi.
-我认识你 -没错 你认识
- I know you. - Yeah, you do.
他叫本·福特 和我一个班的
This is Ben Ford. He's in my class.
他也是来参观的
He's visiting, too.
你还教过我儿童棒球呢
You were my t-ball coach.
我爸是你的医生 他就在那
My dad's your doctor. He's right over there.
你有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
你想把我大学生活扼杀在摇篮里吗
Are you trying to ruin college for me before I even get here?
不 我不是
No, I-I'm not.
不好意思 你不是什么蠢蛋
I am so sorry. You are not a clown.
你是个很棒的候补游击手
You were an excellent backup shortstop.
艾丽莎 布鲁斯
Alecia. Bruce.
加油 斗牛蛙 斗牛犬队
Go, Bullfrogs-- dogs!
加油 斗牛犬
Go, Bulldogs.
克莱尔
Claire!
哇 真的吗
Wow. Really?
不是 只是很震惊啊
No, it's just a shock, is all.
杰
Jay?
这么说西莉亚怀着法官的孩子
So Celia's carrying the judge's baby.
怪不得她开枪射他 孕期狂躁
No wonder she shot him. She's hormonal.
-你跟谁打电话呢 -管家而已
- Who are you talking to? -The housekeeper.
玛利亚 我得挂了 多谢剧透
Maria, I've gotta go. Thanks a lot.
杰 我想让你和曼尼谈谈
Jay, I need you to talk to manny.
-怎么了 -他如果真在干你说的那事
- What? - Well, if he's doing what you think he's doing,
那他需要和一个男人谈谈
Then he needs to talk to a man.
我不想让他感到难堪啊
I don't want him to be ashame of anything.
那么你就不应该让我去
Then you don't want to send me in there.
是啊 但如果他有什么疑问呢
Yeah, but what if-- if he has questions?
如果他不知道该怎么
What if he doesn't know how to--
歌洛莉亚 不论他在经历什么
Gloria, Gloria, whatever he's going through,
他都能自己领悟的
he can work it out himself.
救命 我卡住了
Help! I'm stuck!
不 杰 快去 我求你了
Ay, no, Jay, go. I beg of you!
-快走 快走 -歌洛莉亚
- Go! Go! Go! - Gloria.
我真不愿做这事儿
I'm extremely reluctant to do this.
拜托 快点啦
Please hurry!
不行 这是"妇女不宜"内容
Ay, no. I cannot look at this.
搞什么啊
What the hell?
我下不来了 杰
I can't get down, Jay.
怎么了 曼尼出什么事了
What? What happened to Manny?!
-快告诉我出什么事了啊 -歌洛莉亚
-Ay, somebody say something to me! -Gloria,
没事
It's okay.
进来吧
Come on in.
好的
Okay.
他刚才倒挂在这横梁上了
He was hanging from that bar up there.
啥 为什么啊 你头上戴的什么东西
What? Why? What do you have on your head?
加重头盔 通过伸展身体来让我长高
It's a weighted helmet to stretch me so I can get taller.
曼尼 你为什么非要长高啊
Manny! Why do you have to get tall now?
为了爱情 妈妈 还会为什么
Love, mom. Why else?
我的贝拉跟德克斯跑了
I lost Bella to Durkus because,
按她的话说就是"人家好高啊"
in her words, "He's tall."
班里的同学都越长越高 除了我
Everybody else is getting taller but me.
你觉得这是咖啡惹的祸吗
You think it's the coffee?
不是
No.
有可能 但是
Maybe. But--
可是你这样"倒挂金钟"也是做无用功啊
But hanging downside up is not gonna help you.
网上说可以的
The web site said it would.
听着 曼尼
Listen, manny,
你已经集美貌 智慧 风趣于一身了
You're already intelligent and beautiful and funny.
如果你再长高点 你就过于完美了
If you get tall, you're going to have everything,
其他那些歪瓜裂枣
And those poor boys
怎么再和你相提并论呢
Are not gonna have anything to compete with you.
看看这
Look at this.
你头上都有个伤痕了
You have a mark on your head now.
我给你拿些冰来 好不好
I'm gonna go get you some ice, okay?
话倒挺好听的 可我明天怎么办啊
That's a lot of pretty words, but they don't help me tomorrow.
抱歉 孩子 都浮云而已
Sorry, kid. It's just one of those things.
该长高时候自然就会长高
You get taller when you get taller.
你应该睡觉了吧
Why don't you get ready for bed?
老天
Ah, jeez.
我像你这么大的时候
You know, when I was your age,
我靠健身来吸引女生
I started working out to get the girls.
你觉得有用吗
You think that would help?
没错 明天 我们一起去健身
Yeah. So tomorrow, we start working out.
好不好
Okay?
要不然我来给你做几个引体向上
Maybe I'll even show you a few pull-ups
就在这玩意上面
On, uh, this bad boy here, huh?
你看见没
You see that?
过不了多久 你也能 这么壮
Pretty soon, that's how strong... you're gonna be.
-谢了 妈妈 -嘘
- Thanks, mom. - Shh!
-我不想让他们知道我在这 -好的
- I don't want them to know I was here. - Okay.
克莱尔 我就知道是你
Oh, Claire, I thought that was you.
谢天谢地 快进来
Thank god. Come in.
不行 因为我病了 记得不 抱歉
I can't. 'cause I'm sick, remember? Sorry.
其实 我DVD机坏了
Well, my DVD player just broke,
我们都没看到《乱世佳人》的结局是什么
and none of us know how "Gone With the Wind" Ends.
但你看过 对吧
But you saw it, right?
-是克莱尔吗 -是
- Oh, is that Claire? - Yeah.
能告诉我们结局吗
Can you tell us what happened?
我能 但我不想给你们剧透啊
I could, but I don't want to ruin it for you.
不会 我们真的想知道 我们真的想
No, we really need to know. We need to know.
克莱尔 快告诉我们吧
Claire. Just tell us. -Um...
郝思嘉真的很生克拉克·盖博的气
Scarlett is... really mad at Clark Gable
因为他说了很多不好听的话
Because, um, he says so many bad things.
是不是 还把 一农场什么的给点了
And didn't he, um, burn down a farm or something?
克莱尔 你是不是醉了
Claire, have you been drinking?
我喝了点苏格兰热托地 喉咙有点不舒服
I had a hot toddy. Made one for my throat.
晚上卧床的话 你这也穿的太光鲜了吧
Pretty dressed up for a night in bed, right?
我只是随手拿了件衣服穿
Yeah, I-I just threw on the first thing I could find...
卢克打电话来时 正好那件就在椅子上
when Luke called, and it was just right there on the chair.
看她手上还盖着章呢
She has a stamp on her hand.
好吧
Okay. All right.
在大家点亮火把 群起而捉奸之前
Before we bust out the pitchforks and the torches,
可别忘了
May I remind you
我曾经帮你们把孩子都送回家
that I've driven every one of your children home
还急救过至少一个 贝瑟妮
and heimliched at least one, Bethenny.
-大家好 -你好
- Hi. - Hello.
说来尴尬 我能借用下洗手间吗
This is totally inappropriate. But could I use your bathroom?
抱歉 你一直灌我喝酒
Sorry. You kept pushing the drinks.
他是我朋友 同志朋友
I--friend. Gay friend. Gay.
-我不是同志 -你必须得是
- I-I'm not gay. -Yes, you are.
我不是同志 我只是法国人
I-I'm not gay. I'm--I'm french.
你以为我是同志
You thought I was gay?
-你是认真的吗 -你对我是"认真的"吗
- Are you serious right now? - Well, are you?
你整晚都在投怀送抱
You've been throwing yourself at me all night.
哪有 我才没有呢
No, no. No, I have not.
-贝瑟妮 拿葡萄酒来 有好戏看了 -贝瑟妮 别听她的
- Bethenny, grab the pinot. - Bethenny, do not grab the pinot.
你在我面前脱衣服 还捏我的手臂
You undressed in front of me. You squeezed my arm.
你还让我替你按摩 那些都算什么
You asked me for a massage. What was all that?
那时我以为你是个同志
That was--that was me safely objectifying a gay person.
天哪 克莱尔
Wow, Claire!
当时我在年鉴里写"永远别变"
When I wrote "Don't ever change" in your yearbook,
可不是这个意思啊
I didn't mean it like this.
放轻松 霍丽
Oh, ease up, Holly.
我是撒谎了
Okay, I lied.
我是撒谎了 我好不容易得到个自由之夜
I lied, but I get one night to myself,
我只想和风趣的同志朋友纵情欢乐
and I just wanted to spend it with some fun gay people.
这人决定变直又不是我的错
It's not my fault this one decided to be straight.
我从来就是直的
I've always been straight.
你没资格说话
Oh, you don't get to talk!
我居然还向你咨询了时尚观点
I took fashion advice from you!
天哪 我穿这身衣服好看吗
Oh, my god. Do I even look good in this dress?
不 绝不问你了
No. Not you.
太短了 是吧
It's really short, isn't it?
的确
It's short.
是啊
Yeah.
求你了
Please?
求你了 就听我说几句
Please, just listen to me for one second.
离我远点 别跟着我
Go away! Stop following me!
能告诉我为何要骚扰这位女士吗
Hey, you wanna tell me why you're bothering this young lady?
不是的 警官 这是我女儿 快告诉他
Oh, no, no, no, no. Officer, this is my daughter. Tell him.
今晚 我根本不认识你
Tonight, I don't know who you are.
她是在开玩笑
She's... she's joking.
我可不是危险人物
I'm not dangerous.
实际上 我还曾帮这条小路装过灯泡呢
In fact, I-I-I helped to put all the lights on this path.
20年前的事了
20 years ago,
我和朋友一些朋友参加完"维护女性"运动
some friends and I took back the night. So...
我想我刚刚
I-I think I just...
-有点让她难堪了 -只是有点吗
- I embarrassed her a little. - "A little"?
程度过轻 你那衣服才叫让我有点难堪
That sweatshirt embarrasses me "A little."
是女儿 鉴定完毕
Yep, that's a daughter.
今晚是怎么了
Tonight was insane.
你干吗要表现得那样
Why did you have to act like that?
你正在参加一个派对
You were at that party.
我看到你正和某个兄弟会男孩说活
I see you talking to frat boys, and--
这不就是此行的目的吗 感受大学校园
Isn't that why we're here, so I can experience college?
要是我真来了大学 你会怎么做
I mean, what are you gonna do when I actually go?
不知道 也许会抓狂
I don't know. Freak out, I think.
听着
Look...
你长这么大 都是我在保护你
Your whole life, my job has been to protect you--
甜蜜的负担
A job I kinda love.
现在看来我不得不提前退休了
Now I feel like I'm being forced into early retirement.
我只是想找到你 确保你安然无恙
I just needed to find you and make sure you were okay...
坚守到最后一口气在
For as long as I still get to do that.
你总是这样
Just like you--
惹我发火然后又让我感动
Piss me off and then say something sweet.
我要到秋季才走呢
I'm not leaving until the fall.
也许那时能找到个方法
Maybe by then I can figure out
设计出什么东西保护着你
how to put a force field around you.
我一直在寻求解决之道
I've been working on that one
自从第一次帮你系安全带起就开始了
Since the first time I tried to fasten you into your car seat.
当时我把你绑的太紧了
I pinched your chunky little thigh.
虽然你这是在间接说我胖
Even though you basically just called me fat.
好了
So...
这真的很好玩吗
Is it really fun?
什么
What?
不会吧
No!
我们都纠结于为人之限
We all struggle with limitations...
有一些我们愿意接受
Some we're willing to accept...
我现在只想回家
You know, I just wanna be home,
靠着沙发读点书
reading on opposite ends of the sofa.
还有一些我们不愿接受
And some we're not.
我那样做太尴尬了
I'm so embarrassed I did that.
你只是做那个 我们很欣慰
I'm just so happy that that was all it was.
怎么 你以为我在做什么
Why? What'd you think I was doing?
永葆童心也未尝不可
It's never too late to grow in life.
天哪
Oh, my god!
有了我们的专利助长器
"Thanks to our patented lengthenator,
您将最高能增高4英寸
you can increase your height by up to 4 inches."
难以置信 他居然花了50美元来买
I can't believe he would spend $50 on this thing.
就是嘛
I know.
这些钱都够他订两年的花花公子了
He could've got a 2-year subscription to "Playboy" For that.
他不会去订什么花花公子
He's not getting the "Playboy" Ever! Ow!
他只是个小孩
He's a little boy!
等我们明早起来会不会发现
Wouldn't it be great if we woke up tomorrow
我们的车已经回来了
and our car had found its way home?
我觉得事情不会这么发展
Yeah, I feel that's not the way it's gonna happen.
我在农场就遇到过
Happened on the farm one time.
一场龙卷风卷走了我们的一头牛犊
A tornado scooped up one of our calves,
谁知道卷到哪去了 可六个月后
Dropped it who knows where. Six months later,
一头成年牛沿着车道走回来了
A full-grown cow comes walking up the driveway--
一样的花纹 一样的叫声
Same markings, same moo.
-那晚 我们 -我们大餐了一顿
- That night, we-- - We ate like kings.
之前我说过这故事
Okay, I've told it before.
我的天哪 那是我们的车
oh, my gosh! It's our car!
看来你们见过我老婆了
I see you've met my wife.